Hey guys, it's Amanda Seals here at 25 Words or Less.
I want to share with you some of my favorite things.
Just take my word for it.
A great podcast?
My podcast, Small Doses.
You can listen to it wherever you get your podcasts
and you can watch it on YouTube at AmandaSealsTV.
An 80s movie that still holds up?
Coming to America!
One of the greatest of all time!
To be loved!
Aha!
A life hack?
If you ever get fruit flies, get a cup,
put apple cider vinegar in it,
put some plastic over it, poke some holes.
They're rather there in a day.
A mood booster?
Cold shower.
I know, it sounds unpleasant,
but the science says it releases more endorphins
and I can prove it to you.
It does!
A comedian to watch out for?
My homeboy, Reg Thomas.
He opens for me on tour,
he gives me great tips,
and he's got amazing material of his own.
Go-to late night snack?
Uh, hello?
Night cheese!
Everybody loves a little bit of night cheese!